indiantradecenter.com 2015-06-10

# IndianTradeCenter - Indian Manufacturers Suppliers Exporters Directory

While appreciating the users concern for his/ her privacy, this statement discloses the practices being followed by **IndianTradeCenter** in this regard.We request all our users to read the following 'privacy policy' to understand how their personal & business information will be treated, as they make the fullest use of our services to their benefit.

## Collection of Information :

  * When you Register with IndianTradeCenter, you will be asked to complete a registration form which requires you provide information such as your name, address, phone/fax number, email address and other personal information as well as your businessinformation . We terms this as 'Registration Information'.
  * If you post any information to **IndianTradeCenter** to be published on the Website through the publishing tools, including but not limited to Company Profile, Product Catalogs, Sell offers, Buy Leads, Profile and any discussion forum, then you are assumed  to have given consent to the publication of such information . We term this as **‘Publishing Information’.**
  * If you establish a credit account with us or if you purchase a product or service from **IndianTradeCenter,** we may collect additional information, including billing information, credit card numbers and expiration dates and tracking information from cheques or money orders. We term this as **'Payment Information'**. 
  * We also gather usage statistics such as pages viewed, number of unique visitors, browser software,IP addresses, number of sessions, screen resolution etc. for analysis that helps us provide you improved user experience and services. We term this as **‘Statistical Information’**.

## Safety Measures :

  * We engage commercially & technologically reasonable security measures to prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy and ensure correct use of information.As a Registered User, your Registration Information, Publishing Information and Payment Information (if any) can be viewed and edited through your Account which is protected by Password.
  * We recommend that you do not reveal your Password to anyone. Our personnel will never ask you for your Password in an unrequested phone call or in an unrequested e-mail. In case, if you share your computer with others, you should not choose to save your log-in information on the computer.Doremember to sign out of your Account and close your browser window when you have finished your session.

*No data transmission over the Internet or any wireless network can be guaranteed to be perfectly secured. As a result, while we try to protect your information, no web site or company, including ourselves, can absolutely ensure or guarantee the security of any information you transmit to us and you do so at your own risk.

## Changes in Privacy Policy :

  * The policy may change from time to time so please check periodically. Though, we will try to post the changed and restated Privacy Policy on our Website.If you do not agree to the new changes in our Privacy Policy, you should contact IndianTradeCenter in writingand specifically request toreturn or destroy your Collected Information.
